(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series are fictional and created for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
All the promotional videos for the brand.
Please give a round of applause to Prim Pariyakorn Rungruengsuk,
my girlfriend.
There’s no need for us to get to know each other anymore.
Let’s call it quits.
I won’t go to your condo again.
When I set my sights on something,
I’ve never missed.
In the end,
the person who told me not to cross the line
broke the rule herself.
Why did they break up?
Bambi still couldn’t get over her ex.
Don’t leave me, Bambi.
I’m here now.
SCENE: INT. RESTAURANT - NIGHT
CHARACTERS: BAMBI & PRIM
BAMBI WAITS FOR PRIM TO CELEBRATE HER BRTHDAY TOGETHER.
PRIM CAN’T COME. SHE IS TIED UP WITH WORK.
Hello, Prim.
I’m going to be a bit late.
The filming is wrapping up late.
I’ll go there as soon as I finish.
You know today is my birthday.
Why did you take the job?
This is my last year in college.
I got a chance to work as a director's assistant.
I can’t pass on the opportunity.
You know I work really hard.
Bambi, I’m sorry.
You are not mad at me, right?
No.
I’m not mad at you.
I like seeing you happy.
(You should go back to work.)
Focus on the work and hurry to see me.
Okay, I’ll hurry to see you. Bye.
Prim, are you ready?
Yes. I’m coming.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
Happy birthday, my girlfriend.
Make a wish.
Let’s break up.
Bambi.
Why did you say that?
I told you this work is important to me.
I know how much this work means to you.
What about me?
Do I mean anything to you?
I want to be your priority.
I want to be the first one that you think of.
I don’t get why I have these questions when I’m your girlfriend.
I’m sorry.
It won’t happen again.
It’s okay, Prim. I get it.
It will happen again.
I’m trying. Don’t you see?
Yes.
But it’s not enough for me.
I’m self-centered.
When I’m in a relationship, I want to be her priority.
I can’t ask you to leave everything to do what I want.
I think it’s never going to work between us.
No.
Calm down.
I think I can do it.
I can handle work and take care of you.
You can stop trying.
I don’t want to be your burden anymore.
My birthday wish this year.
I wish you success in everything you’ve been working for.
One day, when we are both ready, we can get back together.
But I think we should be just friends for now.
SCENE: INT. BLOSSOM - NIGHT
CHARACTERS: PRIM & BAMBI
PRIM AND BAMBI GET BACK TOGETHER AND THEY ARE VERY MUCH IN LOVE.
Min.
Look.
That couple.
I set them up.
Ant.
Can I have a cocktail?
Sure. What do you want to order?
Sex on Fire.
What do you want to drink?
Kiss Me More.
You’re talking about the cocktail, right?
Sure.
I’ll go to the bathroom.
Are you here to get some air?
You two were kissing for so long.
Stop teasing me.
It’s not wrong to reignite the spark.
Ant.
Do you sell dog food as a snack?
I’m going to eat it as a drinking snack.
Ant, help me.
Stop nagging her.
Look at my girlfriend and me.
We’ve been on and off several times.
Look at us now.
How are you two doing?
We are getting married.
See? Look.
Sometimes, you need to spend time apart to know how you really feel.
Maybe this time, it will last until death parts you.
Thank you for taking my side. But to no need to mention death.
I’ll go to the bathroom.
You, a straight switches teams.
I may switch teams,
but I surely won’t go back to my ex.
You two.
Min.
You are her friend.
If she refuses to listen to you,
all you can do is be there for her.
Just do what you can. Get it?
That’s between them. Let them decide.
Trust me.
Let’s talk about you.
You need to pay for your drinks and the penalty fee.
What?
I know…
what you and Praew did in my bar the other day.
What did I do?
Let’s take pictures.
Sure.
One, two.
Relax, Min.
You look great, Min.
What about me?
You look great, too.
But less than her.
Isn’t it obvious?
-I think it’s obvious. -What is obvious?
No matter how tired I am,
I have C Young to keep me young.
Cut. Great.
Let’s move on to the next scene.
Please hurry and get changed.
Go into the tent and change your outfit.
You need to hurry. The crew is on a tight schedule.
Sure. I’ll do as you want, my stylist.
Shasha.
There are many people outside.
It’s normal for a stylist to help a model get changed.
No one will suspect it.
Aren’t you going to thank me
for helping you get a high-paying job like this?
Thank you?
The client chose me to work on this project.
Don’t you know that I made the request?
I also asked for a raise for you.
I didn’t ask you to do it.
You get hooked on me.
I can’t help it.
Shasha.
What are our rules?
We are doing it only in a private space.
Be professional.
Separate work from play.
I’m not playing around.
What?
Will you go to a concert with me?
No, I don’t like being in the crowd.
Come on. I have no one to go with.
Please.
Hurry and get changed. I’ll think about it.
Sure.
I want to invite you to go up to my room.
But Boom is probably in the room.
It’s okay.
I have something else to do after this.
You can do this when we’re in the car.
But not outside.
I know.
I know where and when I can do it.
Come on.
Your window film is pretty dark.
No one will see us.
Come on.
That’s it.
I’m leaving.
TEXT ME WHEN YOU GET HOME.
Hey.
So you two are dating?
No.
But it’s getting close.
She seems to like me a lot.
Are you sure you’re not imagining it?
She might see you as a phase.
What makes you think that?
She is a straight woman who has just gotten out of a relationship.
She might be looking for new challenges.
So she dates a woman.
In the end, she will go back to dating men.
Do you think she will stay with you?
I think
you should…
date one of us.
It’s okay.
I like her.
I can’t move on from her.
Hi, hi.
Aren’t you too dressed up to play badminton?
No.
Every time I go out is the chance to dress up.
I haven’t played badminton for ages.
The last time was when I played with you in college.
Good.
I take you out to exercise to boost your endorphins.
So you will feel happy.
Just getting back with you,
my endorphin level is already skyrocketing.
You are cute.
Come on. Let’s see if you can beat me.
When I was in high school, I was a top athlete.
Sure.
I’ll show you who the real number one is.
If I win, will you have a prize for me?
What do you want?
I can give you everything.
Is that so?
-Is that so? -Yes.
-Is that so? -What do you want?
Let’s play. Stop joking around.
I’ll beat you.
Come on.
I told you.
I, Bambi,
never lose to anyone.
I’m going easy on you.
Don’t you have sportsmanship, Prim?
Can’t you let me win?
Okay, okay.
I’ll let you win.
What do you want?
Do you want…
an omakase dinner at a rooftop restaurant?
Or a luxurious spa treatment that matches your lifestyle?
Those things, I can buy them myself.
What do you want?
I want…
to sleep over at your place.
I want to spend time with you like when we were in college.
Stay in the dorm near the campus,
where the owner always overcharged me for the electricity bill.
I never missed it.
Never?
But we had many good memories there.
Actually, I missed the time
when we blew out the birthday candles in the bathtub.
Let’s eat a cake.
Yes.
Can we eat it now?
Why not?
Come on.
I want to eat a cake.
Why are you leaving so soon?
It’s still early in the morning.
I have work to do.
I haven’t prepared outfits for the shooting tomorrow.
We are going to a concert this evening.
You didn’t forget it, right?
No.
I’m leaving.
Wait.
Can I hold you before you go?
That’s enough.
A bit longer.
-Shasha. -A bit longer.
Shasha.
You have a schedule today. Did you forget it?
You have a fitting for the fashion week.
If Mac knows that you’re late, he’ll kill you.
He doesn’t like waiting.
I totally forgot it, Woon.
I’m sorry.
I’ve got to go take a shower.
I’ll be right back.
Now, you’ve become her regular partner?
It’s not that often.
I’m going to warn you.
I know Shasha well.
She will never get serious with you.
She can choose anyone she wants.
All her exes are celebrities and models.
I don’t want you to be too into her.
Thank you.
But I’m not that into her.
I know what I’m doing.
Thank you for your warning,
but it’s unwanted.
Where is Gorya?
She left. She said she didn’t want to wait.
Sha, don’t do this next time.
Don’t hang out with someone who distracts you from work.
Woon, it has nothing to do with Gorya.
I forgot it.
-I’m going to take a shower. -Hurry up. We’re already late.
I really like your work.
Are you also working as a photographer?
Yes.
I can take pictures for all kinds of events.
I hired her to shoot behind-the-scenes pictures.
She is really good at it.
That’s great.
Can I have your contact info?
I’ll hire you for other work.
Sure.
I’ll pay you via QR code scan.
Let’s take a picture for the photo handover.
One, two, three.
Done.
Thank you so much.
If you have work for me, please feel free to call me.
Sure. I’ll see you.
Sure. Thank you.
Thank you, Min.
You don’t need to thank me.
It’s all because of your talents.
I helped you a little.
You got your first sale.
More will follow.
Good.
I need money. I need to get a new apartment.
Why? What happened?
Boom just confessed her feelings for me.
She’s my roommate.
What are you going to do?
I rejected her.
She is someone I trust, but now she has feelings for me.
I get it.
If you don’t feel the same way,
you can’t force it.
Yes.
It’s too bad to lose a friend like this.
We’ve known each other for a long time.
You two can still be friends.
You just need to set a boundary.
Don’t lead her on…
that you can be more than friends.
You should tell yourself that.
Don’t talk back at me.
I’m just teasing you.
I’ll help you find a condo.
A photographer with potential like you, you will make a lot of money soon.
Then you can buy your own condo.
Let’s go.
Let’s celebrate your first sale.
Yeah.
Your ankle is not fully healed.
Why did you ask me to go work out with you?
Your ankle might hurt again.
It doesn’t hurt.
I just…
want you to take care of me.
So you are pretending?
If I knew getting back together would be this good,
I would have done it a long time ago.
You are willing to get hurt to have me back?
For you, I can do more than that.
You don’t need to do anything.
I’ll take care of you anyway.
Look.
If I came back too late, I would regret it for the rest of my life.
You are so adorable.
Hi. Min.
Hello, Bambi.
I should go.
I’ll give you a ride.
It’s okay.
I already called my ride.
Bye, Min.
Bye.
You’re taking such great care of the chick.
If the chick grows up and bites you, I’ll laugh at you.
Bambi’s leg hurts.
I just take care of her. That’s all.
Are you free this evening?
Let’s go see a concert.
A client hired us to shoot a music video.
She gave me concert tickets.
Sure.
Hey.
Can I get another ticket for Bambi?
Sure.
What?
Why do you keep teasing me about this?
I never teased you about Praew.
A lesbian newbie like you should be careful.
Be careful of what?
A pretty girl changing to a lesbian is rare.
She seems to be really into you.
I don’t think she wants to be just your experiment.
I don’t mind it.
I like her too.
But I have my own process.
A straight girl like you
enjoys playing with the hearts of lesbians.
Thank you.
Sure.
Wait a sec. Gorya.
Where are you going?
You keep me waiting for too long.
I thought this was your fan meeting.
If you want to date me, you need to get used to it.
Who wants to date you?
I’m sorry, but I don’t understand you.
I’ve never experienced anything like this.
I’m not in the same league as you.
What’s going on?
Shasha.
Wow, Gorya.
Hello, Gorya.
Hey, Bambi.
I can’t believe that you came to this concert.
I’m here to do research for a music video.
I…
I tagged along as the director’s girlfriend.
When did you two become close?
I thought you kept it strictly business.
You attend the concert together like you are a couple.
A couple?
We are just friends.
But you two look good together.
No need to set me up with someone.
I can find my own girlfriend.
Gorya.
I’ll have one champagne.
Hello.
Yes?
Are you Krystal’s fan?
Yes, her songs are beautiful.
I’m looking forward to her new album.
Do you mind if we chat for a bit?
I think you are cute.
No, thank you.
But I really want to get to know you.
I want to find someone who shares similar interests.
I’m sorry. I have a girlfriend.
I’m waiting for her.
Min.
That’s my girlfriend.
Is she really your girlfriend?
You two…
look more like sisters.
What do I need to do to make you believe me?
Do you believe me now?
Okay.
I believe you.
Here is your champagne.
Min.
Aren’t you going to explain to me?
You suddenly kissed my cheek and said I was your girlfriend.
I will take it seriously.
Hold it right there.
She made a move on me, but I don’t want it.
Can’t you help me?
Then date me for real.
So you won’t need to lie.
Don’t take advantage of the situation.
I didn’t take advantage.
This could hurt my reputation.
You need to take responsibility for it.
What do you want?
Kiss my other cheek.
Not here.
Fine.
I’ll take a rain check.
Can I order a drink?
Let’s go see Prim.
She should have arrived.
Here.
We should call a truce.
Since we now have different targets.
I don’t have a target.
I never pick a fight with anyone.
You are the one
who keeps provoking me.
What?!
Do you still want Prim?
Don’t you get that she sees you only as a sister?
I get it.
You don’t need to remind me.
You keep messing with me like this.
Is it because you feel insecure that Prim might be swayed?
I’m not messing with you.
I just want to be your friend.
I like you.
You are quite a fighter.
A fighter?
If I were a fighter,
I would have hit you a long time ago.
Why don’t we give it a try?
Just kidding.
You and Shasha seem like a good match.
It’s not your business.
I don’t want to pry into your business.
I just want to warn you.
Shasha was the same type of person as me.
We like to play games.
When the prey plays hard to get,
we just play along.
When the prey falls for us, we will pull away…
and ditch her.
Think of it as advice from a good friend.
Hey.
What’s going on with Shasha and Gorya?
As you see.
That’s wicked.
She keeps it lowkey.
Unlike us, we made it public.
You also keep it lowkey.
Why don’t they go public like us?
-Bambie. -What?
You look cute today.
You ask me out on a date.
So I need to dress up.
This is not a date.
I came here for work.
So I let you tag along.
Work?
Look around you.
They are here for a date.
Prim and Bambi.
Over there.
Gorya and Shasha. I’m sure they are on a date.
Except us.
You are imagining things.
You called me your girlfriend.
Then you’ll be my girlfriend for tonight.
Do you want to stand with her?
No, it’s annoying.
Hello, everyone.
Thank you for attending the event of my new album release, The Dreamer.
I saw many familiar faces today.
I’ll open the show with the song that made me become widely known.
This song means a lot to me and someone special.
It’s one of the songs that I dearly cherish.
♪ Can you feel it like I do? ♪
♪ Every moment passing through ♪
♪ For me, it’s all dedicated to you ♪
♪ Since the day we met ♪
♪ You showed me what longing was ♪
♪ Now I know what love is ‘cause I have you ♪
♪ And it isn’t just fate ♪
♪ No one else could ever take your place ♪
♪ It’s only you ♪
♪ You’re more than the word “love” ♪
♪ What you are to me, my love ♪
♪ Just a glance, just a touch ♪
♪ This love will always belong to us ♪
♪ My love, every time I hear the word “love” ♪
♪ You’re the only one I’m thinking of ♪
♪ I just want you to know ♪
♪ These arms are yours forevermore, my love ♪
The music here is nice.
It sounds so in love.
How is it?
Did you get ideas for the music video?
Yes.
I want to make a GL music video.
Music video with two female leads, I have never done it before.
You pick up an idea from what you are familiar with.
I know you can do it well.
My girlfriend is talented.
You are complimenting me too much.
You don’t need to believe in me that much.
If I don’t compliment you, who else would I compliment?
Someone takes pictures of us again.
You need to get used to it.
I’m telling you.
You and Shasha are popular.
You are the type that women like.
Me?
Yes.
Can you stop comparing me to Shasha?
I’m just an aspiring director.
She is an international model. I’m not in the same league as her.
Why?
You two are very similar.
You are pretty, talented, and confident.
I think you two can be friends.
Stop pushing.
I have enough friends.
What’s going on with you?
Why do you want me to be her friend badly?
I just want everyone to get along.
Please practice what you preach.
Can you be nice to Gorya?
She’s like a sister to me.
Stop feeling jealous.
No matter who makes a move on me, I won’t be interested.
When was I not nice to her?
-I can’t remember it. -All the time.
-Really? -Yes.
I don’t know.
I’ll keep an eye on you.
Make sure she is just like a sister.
If she calls you with a sweet voice.
Prim, what do you think about that dress?
What do you think about this dress?
Don’t let me catch you doing that.
I’m going to congratulate Kris.
Why don’t you come with me?
No. I don’t know her.
Then you should get to know her.
She is popular right now.
You may get a new job from her.
Kris.
Sha.
I thought you wouldn’t come.
Congratulations. Your new song is amazing.
Thank you.
I’m the muse for your first album.
Of course, I have to come.
Who is the inspiration for your second album?
No one.
I’m single.
It’s more fun to write a song from someone else’s story.
Sha.
Are you single?
Do you have any fun stories for me to write a song about?
What is going on between you and her?
Is she your new girlfriend?
No.
Kris, this is Gorya.
My stylist.
I thought she was your new girlfriend.
You are cute.
I really want to know who will be your next girlfriend after me.
That will be hard.
You set the bar high.
Who can compete with you?
It’s not easy to be my girlfriend.
That’s true.
You are picky.
A little.
Are you still living in the same place?
Of course. Where else can I move to?
I’ll visit you when I have free time.
Sure.
Shasha, I’m leaving.
Congratulations, Krystal.
Your new song is amazing.
Are you going to party with us?
I want to get to know you.
We may have a chance to work together in the future.
Maybe next time.
I have to work tomorrow.
That’s too bad.
It’s okay.
I’ll be right back.
Gorya.
Gorya, where are you going?
I’m going home to rest.
Okay.
Are you jealous because of Kris?
Aren’t you a bit full of yourself?
Then what?
Did Woonsen say something to you?
No one said anything to me.
I’m just tired.
I want to rest.
Then go to my condo and rest.
No.
Why do I need to go there often?
You should go back and enjoy the night with her.
Okay.
There’s nothing between Kris and me.
You are someone special to me.
You are my only one.
Thank you.
But you don’t need to give me any title.
We are not that compatible.
Our friend with benefits deal. Let’s call it off.
I’m done.
You came to my door and made the offer.
I didn’t force you to do it.
Yes, I was wrong.
Now, I’ve come to my senses.
Happy?
Let’s go back to my condo and talk.
No.
I have my own home.
I’m going home to rest.
What is wrong with you?
I just want you to come home with me.
Don’t do this again.
Otherwise, my anger…
will turn into hatred.
I’m sorry for keeping you waiting.
I was talking to my client.
It’s okay.
You can take as much time as you want.
I’ll wait for you.
Come on. Let’s go home.
I’ll give you a ride home.
No.
I don’t want to go home yet.
I don’t want this date to end yet.
You’re trying hard to insist that this is a date.
Fine, it’s a date.
Let’s go.
Ouch.
You bumped into my head.
Bambi.
What?
-Sit here. -Where?
Hey, I’m not that drunk.
Then why did you let me carry you? You are heavy.
Heavy?
I’m petite.
I’m easy to carry like a miniature.
Hey.
Where are you going?
Hold me.
I’ll go get water and aspirin for your hangover in the morning.
Don’t go.
I’m drunk on nothing.
I’m drunk on you.
I pretend to be drunk for your attention.
Prim, Prim, Prim.
I noticed it.
You barely drank.
Because you want to take care of me.
Just like when we were in college.
When we went to a nightclub, you only had two drinks.
You kept an eye on me so I wouldn’t go up and dance on stage.
When I tried to stop you, have you ever listened to me?
Before I could take you down,
you had already become a star of the nightclub near our campus.
We had a great time back then.
But I’m going to make today…
even better.
Good.
Stop talking about the past.
Back then,
I was too focused on the work that I forgot about you.
Now, I can balance my priorities. I’m a new person.
You don’t need to choose me over work.
Now, I get it.
Work is important to you.
I was unreasonable back then.
I wanted things to go my way.
That’s enough.
Stop talking about the past.
Let’s focus on the present.
My future.
If you are not a part of it,
I will never be happy.
I want you to be by my side when I fall
and when I win an award.
But…
You’ve won an award.
My all-time favorite girlfriend award.
I don’t expect anything from you.
If you are happy when you take care of me,
then you should do it.
You need to stop being nosy and mind your own business.
You got played by your manager and don’t even realize it.
What do you mean?
After you broke up with me, are you really dating a woman?
-Being a lesbian is more exciting? -Praew.
We are closed.
Can you hold me?
I just want to feel that I am wanted.
I will only hold you.